

PROFILE

I am a professional creative designer with a deep passion for helping people solve problems. I pride myself on being able to develop intuitive and consistent user experiences from conception to implementation.

With 6+ years of experience in studying and applying numerous user behaviour models, I have become very adept at developing interfaces that are able to scale and run on multiple modern platforms.

I have a keen interest in emerging technologies and relish taking on new opportunities that will allow me to further develop my skill set to reach new professional milestones.

EDUCATION

2008-2011 **COMPUTING SCIENCE** Northumbria University

2007-2008

BUSINESS & ECONOMICS

Aleppo University

SKILLS

- UI/UX
- Sketch
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- HTML5/CSS3
- JavaScript
- GruntJS

GHIS BAKOUR

SENIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER

Address: 07-03 La Brisa, 50 Lorong 28 Guillemard Street, Singapore 398453

Phone: +65 87 4 88 144

E-mail: fata.suir9@gmail.com//www.fatasuir9.com

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR UI/UX SPECIALIST

iCar Asia Limited | 2015 - 2017

- Design wireframes, and sketch prototypes of upcoming products
- Develop consistent user experiences, and interfaces across all platforms
- Write applications to meet product requirements and technical specifications
- Research, evaluate, and implement technologies to maximise team efficiency
- Provide guidance and mentorship to junior team members

HEAD OF WEB DESIGN

TrustedCompany.com | 2013 - 2015

- Implement product features for the business B2B user experience
- Debug, diagnose and resolve errors in complex software applications
- Establish quality standards and guides to ensure apps perform to specification
- Mentor junior designers helping them tackle challenges that improve their skills

WEB DESIGNER

Asia Venture Group | 2013 - 2013

- Design interfaces for existing systems while improving usability and quality
- Create UI/UX designs for apps that directly affect our rapidly growing user base
- Develop storyboards, and prototypes to effectively communicate design ideas
- Articulate the strategy behind the workflow and why certain decisions are made

FRONT END & WEB DEVELOPER

Mindvalley Labs | 2012 - 2013

- Develop and ship high-quality online apps successfully in a team environment
- Produce proof of concept apps, and set the technical direction of the team
- Debug errors and ensure all codebase is compatible with all browsers
- Convert prototypes into high-quality HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript apps

PLATFORM & WEB DEVELOPER

Motionworks Sdn. Bhd. | 2011 - 2012

- Analyse and implement functional modules together with the project executive
- Ensure online modules are up to date with the UX related technology
- Develop prototypes into functional applications, and afterwards maintenance

INTERESTS

Gadgets / Chinese tea / Martial arts / Computer games